Guide to the May Chen Papers WAG.301
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Proclamation from the Office of the Mayor of New York declaring "Chinese Heritage and Culture Week" January 26, 1987; Mass Rally in Chinatown Poster August 28, 1998 (Box 12)
- NGO Forum on Women (Beijing), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
- Labor Tour to Japan, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6-10, Box 14, Folder 1)
- University of Massachusetts-Amherst Labor Studies Materials, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 11-17)
- Union Anti-Sweatshop Materials, 1988-2010 (Box 14, Folder 2-17, Box 15, Folder 1-20)
- David Dinkins Campaign and Asian Community Materials, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Asian Labor Materials, 1987, 2006-2011 (Box 15, Folder 22-25, Box 16, Folder 1-4)
- Chinese Labor Tours: Journals and Memorabilia, 2005-2011 (Box 15, Folder 5-9)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance Organizing Materials, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 10-17)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 1199 Chinese Activist Training, 2004-2010 (Box 16, Folder 18-19, Box 17, Folder 1-3)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE) Immigrant Project, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
- Health Care Research, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
- Garment Workers Union Files and Triangle Fire Anniversary, 1994, 2005-2008 (Box 17, Folder 6-19)
- Labor Rights Training Materials, 1988-2010 (Box 18, Folder 1-19)
- Photographs: Personal and Labor Tours, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 20-23)
- Collected Video Documentaries, 1988-1997 (Box 19, Video 1-6)
- Video recordings: Speeches, Conferences, and Demonstrations, 1990-2005 (Box 19, Video 7-23)
- Poster: Activist Bill of Rights, undated (Flat-file-folder 2, Tray 2)
- Poster: Tea and Justice (signed), 2007 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS008, Folder 1)